

JHONNY IRIARTE

Software Engineer

yes, I am Jhonny Iriarte Condori, I am 29 years old and I am characterized by my dynamism, joy and perseverance. My passion for learning and facing challenges drives me constantly. I am enthusiastic about bringing my energy to collaborative teams and taking advantage of new opportunities.

Contacto

+591 74320607

iriarte.condori.jhonny25@gmail.

jhonny-iriarte-condori.netlify.app

tiquipaya zn, ciudad de los niños

Educación

Software Engineer

Academio
Full-Stack Web Development
and Computer Science Course
2022-2023

Mexico

Diploma in Banking and Financial Risks

Postgraduate Program from the Faculty of Economic Sciences 2021-2022

Av. José Ballivian y Calle Chuquisaca

Financial Engineering

Universidad Mayor de San Simon 2014-2021

123 Cochabamba calle., calama

Experiencia

Nerds OnSite

Deployment and Management of Digital Services on Linux Servers

Dic 2019 - ago 2023

I worked as an independent contractor in the deployment, implementation, and management of the Zabbix business model as a monitoring system for pfsense devices, ensuring its efficiency and adaptation to the client's needs.

SALCEDO PRO

Social media management

Dic 2018 - ago 2019

As an independent contractor, I played a crucial role in creating and managing posts for platforms such as Facebook, TikTok, and Instagram. Additionally, my contribution extended to structuring the business model, providing ideas that drove its development and growth.

Digital NetWork.srl

Operational Technician in Structured Cabling.

Dic 2011 - Ago 2022

Participé en la parte administrativa como miembro de Recursos Humanos, encargado específicamente de los inventarios. También participé en la primera auditoría de ISO y OSHAS, demostrando responsabilidad, compromiso y honestidad en el desempeño de mis funciones.

Electronics and Telecommunications Technician

CIFA Technical Institute 2008-2011

Padre Bertha Urbanization, Ciudad del Niño

Skills

Organization

Communication

Teamwork

Meeting deadlines

Critical thinking

Idiomas

Quechua

Ingles

Español

Referencias

Ing Boris F. Alfaro Bazan Regional manager Digital NetWork.srl Telef. (591-4) 4123668

Software management.

- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- Node.js
- Postgres SQL
- Taildwind
- 🖣 zabbix
- Linux
- Pfsense
- Githup